maxsteingart.com 2019-06-26

# Max Steingart

Max Steingart, who owns and operates the [www.maxsteingart.com](http://www.maxsteingart.com/) web site, cares about the privacy of each user of our web site. This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for [ www.maxsteingart.com](http://www.maxsteingart.com/) web site.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact [support@maxsteingart.com](mailto:support@maxsteingart.com).

**Information Collection and Use**  
The [www.maxsteingart.com](http://www.maxsteingart.com/) web site collects information from our users at several different points on our web site. When you use the web site, some basic, general information is collected. This general information is used internally in connection with our business to improve the web site, including our marketing and advertising efforts, and to make your use of the web site as enjoyable and efficient as possible.

When you set up an account on our web site or purchase an item from our web site, we collect personal information provided by you that may include your: (i) first and last name; (ii) billing address; (iii) shipping address; (iv) other shipping addresses; (v) email address; (vi) phone number; (vii) credit card account number; (viii) items purchased from us; and (ix) browsing, buying and selling patterns. We use this personal information in order to provide you with the goods and services that you purchase on our web site. We use your email address to provide you with information about your order and its status and we may occasionally send out emails, including newsletters, to people who have placed an order on-line, with information about other goods and services available on our web site. Your phone number is used by us only in the event that our agents need to contact you about an order you have placed.

Max Steingart ("we" or "us") owns and operates the [ www.maxsteingart.com](http://www.maxsteingart.com/) web site and he is the sole owner of this information collected on the web site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to a third party in any way other than as disclosed in this privacy policy. We fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities and may, in our sole discretion, disclose personal information or other information to satisfy any law, regulation, subpoena, or government request. We reserve the right to release personal information or other information about users who we believe are engaged in illegal activities or are otherwise in violation of our Terms of Service, even without a subpoena, warrant or court order, if we believe, in our sole discretion, that such disclosure is necessary or appropriate to operate our web site or to protect the rights or property of [www.maxsteingart.com](http://www.maxsteingart.com/), our affiliates, or our officers, directors, employees, agents, third-party content providers, suppliers, sponsors, or licensor's. We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities we reasonably believe in our sole discretion to be unlawful. If we are legally compelled to disclose information about you to a third party, we will attempt to notify you by sending an email to the email address in our records unless doing so would violate the law or unless you have not provided your email address to us.

 **Registration**  
To use some features on the [www.maxsteingart.com](http://www.maxsteingart.com/) web site, a user must first complete a registration form on the web site. During registration, a user is required to give contact information, such as name and email address. This information is used to contact users about the services on our web site for which they have indicated interest. It is optional for users to provide additional, demographic information, such as age and gender, but we encourage our users to provide such information so that we can provide a more personalized experience for our users on our web site.

 **Orders**  
We request additional personal information from our users when placing an order on our web site. In completing our order form, a user must provide contact information, such as name and shipping address, and financial information, such as credit card account number and expiration date. This information is used for billing purposes and to fulfill our customer orders. If we experience difficulties processing an order, we will contact a user through this information.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a text file stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Many web sites create cookies to record information about a user's preferences, such as the items you add to your shopping cart, and for security purposes (see Security below). Cookies may also used to help us determine the various services you use and the support you may need, and to help us detect and solve any problems you may have while using our web site. Most cookies expire after a certain time period. If you wish, you may set your browser to reject all cookies and still view our web site. 

**Log Files**  
Like most standard web sites, we use log files on our servers. These log files store information regarding IP (internet protocol) addresses, browser type, ISP (internet service provider), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks. These log files are used to analyse trends, administer the web site, track user's movements in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for our use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personal information. In addition, we utilize Google Analytics to evaluate traffic on our website. Google Analytics stores information similar to that described above.

 **Sharing of General or Demographic Information**  
We may share aggregated, general or demographic information we collect about our users and their use of our web site with our third-party partners and advertisers in a manner which does not identify any individual user. We use an outside shipping company to ship orders placed on our web site, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services purchased on our web site. These companies will not retain, share, store or use any of our user's personal information for any secondary purposes. We may partner with other parties to provide specific services which are available on our web site. When a user signs up for these services, we will share the user's name or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services to the user. These parties are not allowed to use such personal information except for the purpose of providing these services.

[www.maxsteingart.com](http://www.maxsteingart.com/) partners with Amazon.com to sell books, CD's and tapes. [www.maxsteingart.com](http://www.maxsteingart.com/) does not pass any personal information to Amazon and no personal information is shared by Amazon back to [www.maxsteingart.com](http://www.maxsteingart.com/). Amazon shares aggregate purchase information with [www.maxsteingart.com](http://www.maxsteingart.com/) for the purpose of determining revenue share.

 **Links**  
The web site contains links to other web sites. We want you to be aware that when you click on such links, including banner advertising, which take you to a third-party web site, you will be subject to such third-party's privacy policies. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other web sites and we expressly disclaim any and all liability for the actions of third-parties, including, without limitation, actions relating to the use and/or disclosure of personal information by such third-parties. We encourage our users to be aware of when they leave our web site and enter a third-party web site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects their personal information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by our web site.

 **Newsletter**  
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we will ask for contact information, such as name and email address. That information is never sold or shared with other organizations.

 **Surveys & Contests**  
From time-to-time, our web site may request information from our users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user has a choice whether or not to provide us with such information. Information requested may include contact information, such as name and shipping address, and demographic information, such as zip code, age level. Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used to monitor or improve the use and efficiency of this web site. This information will never be sold or shared.

 **Security**  
This web site takes precautions we believe are reasonable to protect our users' information. When you submit personal information via our web site, your information is protected by us both on-line and off-line.

When our registration or order form asks users to enter personal information, such as credit card account number or social security number, such information will be encrypted by our encryption software, which is provided by Secure Socket Layer (SSL), before such information is transmitted over the internet. SSL prevents unauthorized people from intercepting your personal data. It is important to use a browser that supports SSL, such as Google Chrome, Apple Safari or Microsoft Internet Explorer. These browsers show a symbol in the status bar, such as a key or a lock, when you are viewing a web site that uses SSL. To learn more about SSL, you may visit their web site at: [http://www.ssl.com](http://www.ssl.com/).

While we use SSL encryption to protect users' personal information on-line, we also protect our users' information off-line. All of our users' information, including both general and personal information, is carefully stored in our offices and the facilities of our web hosting provider. Only employees who use such information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personal information. In addition, the servers that we store personal information on are kept in a physically and electronically secure environment.

We make efforts we believe are reasonable to prevent the alteration, theft, loss or misuse of our users' information by others. However, please keep in mind that there is always some risk in transmitting information over the Internet.

If you have any questions about the security of our web site, you can send an email to [support@maxsteingart.com](mailto:support@maxsteingart.com)

**Communications from our Web Site**  
We send all new members a welcoming email to verify their password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Each user has the option to not receive these types of communications (see Choice/Opt-Out below).

Occasionally, it is necessary to send out service-related announcements. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email informing you of such service interruption. Generally, users may not opt-out of receiving these service-related communications. In addition, we communicate with our users on a regular basis to provide requested services and regarding issues relating to their account via email.

 **Correction/Updating Personal Information**  
If a user's personal information changes or if a user no longer desires our service, we will enable our users to correct, update or remove from our web site the personal data they provided to us. Such changes can be made either through the member information page on our web site or by emailing us at [support@maxsteingart.com](mailto:support@maxsteingart.com).

**Choice/Opt-out**  
Our users are given the opportunity when registering with our web site to opt-out of having their information used for purposes not directly related to the provision of goods or services through our web site. Our membership form has an opt-out mechanism so users purchasing a membership from us may elect to not have their email address added to our marketing and promotional address lists.

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or other marketing and promotional materials from us or our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to any such promotional email indicating your desire to no longer receive such emails or by emailing our us at [support@maxsteingart.com](mailto:support@maxsteingart.com).

Users of our web site will be notified if, in connection with the use of a particular service on our web site, their information will be collected by any outside third-party. At such time, the user can determine whether they wish to proceed with a service that will involve an outside party having access to their information.

 **Collecting Information From Children Younger than 13**  
The [www.maxsteingart.com](http://www.maxsteingart.com/) web site does not knowingly collect or use any personal information from children under the age of 13 without obtaining verifiable parental consent.

 **Notification of Changes in Use of Information**  
Our privacy policy is subject to change. In the event of any change, we will provide notice of such change on our web site. If we want to use your personal information in a manner different from that stated to you at the time you provided such information to us, we will notify you of such change via email in addition to posting notification of such change on our web site. At such time, you can determine whether you wish to allow us to use your information in this different manner. If you have opted out of all communication with our web site or have deleted or deactivated your account with us, then you will not be contacted and your personal information will not be used.

 **If you have any questions about this privacy policy or believe that the[www.maxsteingart.com](http://www.maxsteingart.com/) web site is not abiding by our privacy policy, please contact us by e-mail at [support@maxsteingart.com](mailto:support@maxsteingart.com).**
